Girls! "SEED" is your story!...it is made up of the thoughts you think in secret - good and bad - and since your
thoughts are YOU, so "Seed" is YOU! DOn't fail to see the picture that reaches right into your heart and soul!
Seed is a drama film directed by John M. Stahl.
Bart is a clerk for a publishing company; he has written a novel.
His wife Peggy and he have five children.
Bart's former girlfriend Mildred is manager of the company's Paris office.
She manages to get the novel published and talks Bart
into marrying her after he divorces Peggy.
Initially successful, Bart must turn to writing trash to keep Mildred in money.
When he sees how well his four sons and daughter Margaret have grown without his
help, he asks Peggy to let them all come live with him and Mildred.
Peggy agrees, but the arrival of his beloved children
puts Mildred's future in jeopardy.
Written by Ed Stephan
Bart Carter, played by John Boles.
Mildred, played by Genevieve Tobin.
Peggy Carter, played by Lois Wilson.
Junior Carter, played by Raymond Hackett.
Margaret Carter, played by Bette Davis.
Jennie, played by Zasu Pitts.
Seed is a 1931 American pre-Code drama film directed by John M.
The screenplay by Gladys Lehman is based on a novel by Charles G.
The tone is emotional.